{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261012580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261012579"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" c171491f-fbaa-4e2e-975e-7379840b8cd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..A.all.10.rand.say.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_r_a_i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261024642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261024642"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261026630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261026629"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261028224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261028220"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261030913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261030913"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261032500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261032500"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261036816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261036816"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261038429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261038429"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261041236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261041236"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261042816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261042816"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261045077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261045076"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261046667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261046666"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261048988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261048988"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261050588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261050588"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261052778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261052778"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261054354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261054353"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261056818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261056818"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261058409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261058409"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261060773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261060773"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261062370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261062370"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261064680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261064680"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261066280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261066280"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261068776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261068775"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261070361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261070361"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261072839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261072839"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261074438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261074437"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261076841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261076841"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261078428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261078428"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261080762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261080762"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261082349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261082349"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261084677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261084677"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261086279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261086279"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261088578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261088577"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261090166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261090166"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261092438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261092438"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261094078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261094078"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261096431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261096431"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261097997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261097994"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261100310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261100309"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261101911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261101910"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261104017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261104016"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261105585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261105585"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261110505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261110505"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261112081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261112080"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261114391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261114391"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261115969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261115969"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261118046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261118046"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261119611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261119611"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261125539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261125539"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261127563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261127562"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261127705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261127705"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 751a518f-9d8a-485f-aeb7-97442d70b65a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261141374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261141374"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261147259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261147259"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261152741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261152741"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261158284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261158284"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261163774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261163774"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261169369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261169369"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-4-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261174926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261174926"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_5-8-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261180445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261180445"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261185945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261185945"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261192124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261192124"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261198686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261198685"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 460a9aeb-feff-4933-999e-5a2c28827742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261216340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261216340"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 298e96ac-1706-4a11-a092-12ed9df53552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261217381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261217381"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 298e96ac-1706-4a11-a092-12ed9df53552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261225391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261225391"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 298e96ac-1706-4a11-a092-12ed9df53552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261225511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261225511"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 298e96ac-1706-4a11-a092-12ed9df53552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261271954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261271953"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 298e96ac-1706-4a11-a092-12ed9df53552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261272043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261272043"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b6b41a2b-38d7-4371-846d-5df7a33fff22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261283363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261283363"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261285459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261285459"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261287587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261287587"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261290859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261290859"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261293132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261293132"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261295356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261295356"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261298240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261298240"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261300438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261300437"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261302652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261302652"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261305912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261305912"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261308038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261308038"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261310152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261310152"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261313174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261313173"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261316833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261316833"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261319070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261319070"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261322189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261322189"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261325943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261325942"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261328285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261328285"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261331393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261331393"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261333561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261333561"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261335681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261335681"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261338896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261338895"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261341906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261341906"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261344409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261344409"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261347612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261347612"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261350032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261350032"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261352468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261352468"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261361137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261361137"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261368818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261368817"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261368949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261368949"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 31582fa8-b600-4948-9502-662928cdfed7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261398904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261398904"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_36_43-36-30"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 36"," userResponse":" 30"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261408541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261408541"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_36_43-36-30"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 36"," userResponse":" 36"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261417796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261417796"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_37_43-36-37"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 37"," userResponse":" 37"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261428011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261428010"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_34_41-34-37"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 34"," userResponse":" 34"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261437325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261437325"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_35_33-34-35"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 35"," userResponse":" 33"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261446773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261446772"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_35_33-34-35"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 35"," userResponse":" 34"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261455942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261455942"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_35_33-34-35"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 35"," userResponse":" 35"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261463358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261463357"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_36_43-36-31"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 36"," userResponse":" 31"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261472951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261472950"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_36_43-36-31"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 36"," userResponse":" 43"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261483265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261483264"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_36_43-36-31"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 36"," userResponse":" 31"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261489468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261489467"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_34_33-34-42"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 34"," userResponse":" 33"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261497849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261497849"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_34_33-34-42"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 34"," userResponse":" 34"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261504775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261504775"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_39_41-30-39"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 39"," userResponse":" 30"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261513497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261513497"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 36e4b4b3-9af9-47f3-bc4c-458a30fca7db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.decr.32"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_39_41-30-39"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261531040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261531040"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261539428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261539428"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261540986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261540986"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261544036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261544036"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261545608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261545608"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261547966","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261547966"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261549588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261549587"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261552029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261552029"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261553646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261553646"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261556597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261556597"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261558198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261558198"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261560841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261560841"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261562518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261562517"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261567184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261567184"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261568763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261568762"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261571418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261571418"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261573024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261573024"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261578394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261578394"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" START_BEGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261579357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261579357"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261580977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261580974"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261583607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261583607"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261585284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261585284"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261587555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261587555"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261589121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261589120"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" boga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOGA"," userResponse":" BOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261594154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261594154"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" boga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BOGA"," userResponse":" BOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261595759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261595759"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261600226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261600226"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261602241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261602240"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261602376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261602376"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 57a95a90-5279-460a-84e3-ffccef19d57c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baridi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261643406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261643405"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" d7677780-be01-4f2b-a5de-f43c1b33547b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261663369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261663369"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" d7677780-be01-4f2b-a5de-f43c1b33547b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261687000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261687000"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" d7677780-be01-4f2b-a5de-f43c1b33547b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261705865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261705864"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" d7677780-be01-4f2b-a5de-f43c1b33547b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261729429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261729429"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" d7677780-be01-4f2b-a5de-f43c1b33547b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261729542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261729542"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" d7677780-be01-4f2b-a5de-f43c1b33547b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261739348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261739348"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261739739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261739739"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261740232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261740232"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261740576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261740576"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261740992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261740992"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261741469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261741468"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261741707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261741707"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261744915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261744915"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261744951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261744951"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261745686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261745686"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261746094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261746093"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261746409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261746409"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261746613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261746613"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261746831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261746830"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261747165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261747163"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261747409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261747409"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261750485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261750485"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261750908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261750908"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261753509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261753508"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261753721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261753721"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261753934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261753934"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261763902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261763902"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261768024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261768024"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261774591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261774590"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261777360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261777359"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261777737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261777737"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261778235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261778235"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261778583","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261778583"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261778995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261778995"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261779477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261779477"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261779723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261779723"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261782891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261782891"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261782925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261782925"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261783640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261783640"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261784034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261784034"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261784329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261784329"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261784533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261784533"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261784729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261784728"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261785044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261785044"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261785268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261785268"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261787944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261787943"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261788156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261788156"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b233a161-8906-45d6-a8f1-6aeaeb64001a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261799651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261799651"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261800398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261800397"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261800591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261800591"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261801347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261801347"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261804717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261804717"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" IMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261805480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261805480"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261809697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261809697"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261810619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261810619"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261811457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261811456"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261814978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261814978"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261815832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261815832"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261819855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261819855"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" MAZINGIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261820789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261820788"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261824755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261824754"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" YAMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261825969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261825969"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261829538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261829538"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261830457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261830457"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261831272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261831272"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261834916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261834916"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261835771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261835771"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261838925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261838924"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261839068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261839067"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 53fba31b-3604-4559-ba21-72ca389c91bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261851479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261851479"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261852224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261852224"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261852420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261852420"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261853177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261853177"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shule yetu ni nzuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261856565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261856565"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" IMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261857333","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261857333"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261877224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261877224"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261878159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261878159"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261878974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261878974"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261882640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261882640"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261883512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261883512"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261887406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261887406"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZINGIRA"," userResponse":" MAZINGIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261889143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261889142"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mazingira mazuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261893011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261893011"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMEPANDWA"," userResponse":" YAMEPANDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261894224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261894224"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yamepandwa maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261897808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261897808"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKIENDA"," userResponse":" UKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261898733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261898733"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261899547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261899547"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ukienda ovyo ovyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261903126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261903126"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAHARIBU"," userResponse":" UTAHARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261903978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261903978"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::School_Welcome_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261907130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261907129"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261907262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261907262"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBO"," userResponse":" MAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261915118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261915117"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261921505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261921504"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" e3dde554-eda4-4f5d-a43b-2b19d7520688"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__School_Welcome_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Utaharibu mambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261932884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261932884"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261933259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261933259"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261933744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261933744"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261934088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261934088"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261934514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261934514"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261934994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261934994"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261935221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261935221"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261945739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261945739"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261945780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261945780"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261946494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261946494"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261946888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261946888"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261947184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261947184"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261947391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261947391"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261947587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261947587"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261947912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261947911"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261948149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261948149"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261960129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261960128"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261960536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261960535"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261963141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261963141"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261963363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261963363"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261963577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261963577"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261972640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261972639"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261974511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261974510"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548261974641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548261974641"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262015669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262015668"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262023141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262023141"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 86d47862-d9d9-46e2-83b6-8fffcdb23411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262099424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262099424"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_chungwa-iwapo-panda-mchezo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262114938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262114938"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_dhaifu-chungwa-nafuu-nauli"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262142263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262142263"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_manjano-mungu-samahani-acha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262161616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262161616"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_manjano-twende-u-samawati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262189919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262189919"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_hebu-tofauti-uko-kijani"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262255645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262255645"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_kile-kijani-je-kasi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262255692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262255692"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kijani_kile-kijani-je-kasi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262255898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262255898"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" f429a911-cee2-4d0a-860f-46501683db73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262278009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262278009"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_a_z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262284706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262284706"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_b_g"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262291430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262291429"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262298151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262298151"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_o_b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262304859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262304859"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_b_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262311660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262311659"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262318384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262318384"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_e_r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262325115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262325115"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_r_m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262331796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262331796"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_b"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262338527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262338526"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:B..B.all.10.rand.say.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262345940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262345940"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" b25c6ae4-03bc-47f3-9f66-cca9f64d1359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_B..B.all.10.rand.say.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_b_f_k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262355879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262355879"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 8bc476b1-6448-4609-a9a6-06375caffd76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262380826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262380826"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_192957"," gameId":" 8bc476b1-6448-4609-a9a6-06375caffd76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"end":"end"}]}